<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Mango Distribution System</string>

    <string name="alphonso">The variety is named after Afonso de Albuquerque, a Portuguese general and military expert who helped establish Portuguese colonies in India.[1] The Portuguese introduced grafting on mango trees to produce extraordinary varieties like Alphonso. The fruit was then introduced to the Konkan region in Maharashtra and Goa. The Alphonso is a seasonal fruit, available mid-April through the end of June.[1] The fruits generally weigh between 150 and 300 grams (5.3 and 10.6 oz). They have a rich, creamy, tender texture and delicate, non-fibrous, juicy pulp. The skin of a fully ripe Alphonso mango turns bright golden-yellow with a tinge of red which spreads across the top of the fruit. The flesh of the fruit is saffron-colored.[1] These characteristics make Alphonso a favored cultivar.</string>

    <string name="chaunsa">The fruit has a golden-yellow color when it is soft, is almost fiberless, and has an aromatic, pleasant, sweet flavor. Commonly available varieties in India are greenish-yellow. The unique taste and richness in its flavor makes it a worldwide favorite. Overall, it is considered the best mango in terms of its rich aroma, sweet taste, juicy pulp and high nutritional value.[2]

The season for Chaunsa in Pakistan normally starts at the beginning of June, and ends in the third week of August. It is heavily exported to the Middle East, Europe, and most recently to the United States.[3] There are three known types of Chaunsa mangoes: Honey Chaunsa, Sweet Chaunsa, and White Chaunsa. White Chaunsa is considered best for export due to its longer shelf life.</string>

    <string name="Dasheri">The Dasheri mango is a mango cultivar which originated in a village near Kakori in Lucknow district in 18th century. It is a sweet and fragrant variety of mango grown in North India and the southern state Andhra Pradesh, Nepal and Pakistan. Malihabad in Uttar Pradesh is the largest producer of the Dasheri mango.</string>

    <string name="langra">The Langra mango, also known as Banarasi Langra,[1] is a mango cultivar primarily grown in Banaras, Northern India, Bangladesh and Pakistan.[2][3] This cultivar retains a greenish tinge while ripening. It is normally harvested during the last half of July. Around 2006, it was known to be gaining popularity on the international market.[4] It is considered suitable for slicing and canning.</string>

    <string name="gir_kesar">The Gir Kesar mango, also called Kesar, is a mango cultivar grown in the foothills of Girnar in India. The mango is known for its bright orange colored pulp and was given the geographical indication status in 2011.</string>

    <string name="totapuri">The Totapuri mango, or Ginimoothi, is a cultivar that is widely grown in south India and is partially cultivated in Sri Lanka.[1] It also goes by the names Bangalora, Collector, Kallamai, Kili Mooku, Gilli, Mukku, and Sandersha.[2] In Bengaluru it is referred to as Ginimoothi Maavina Kayi,[3] while most of the rest of India calls it Totapuri or Bangalora. It literally translates to parrot face (gini = parrot, muthi = face).</string>

    <string name="title_activity_details">DetailsActivity</string>

    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>